world things that show our best selves
and that was that was like an that was
an Awakening for us we recognized that's
that feels weird I don't like that I'm
not seeing this transparency into
someone's life but now we grow into an
even more complicated stage a more ugly
stage I argue um a stage where this is
no longer our choice a a stage where as
people and other YouTubers have talked
about a stage where we are into a
automation complacency a place where
you desire
things but you don't know the exact ways
in which you are achieving the desire
right you are somehow watching something
and based on liking something or not
liking something you are being served
more material your life is changing
expanding growing just like a brain
explores thoughts in a way which is not
done by the mechanism of Electro impulse
in your